Guide to the ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records, 1927-1996
5619/006
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union William DuChessi Scott Hoyman Sol Stettin
30 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, and files from the Executive Vice-President's office. During the time period of these records, this office was held by Sol Stetin (Senior Executive Vice-President), William DuChessi (Executive Vice-President), and Scot Hoyman (Executive Vice-President).
ACWA/ACTWU ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors’ and cutters’ locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW’s craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership’s advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards’ by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor’s involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman’s participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor’s Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman’s prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union’s political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union’s existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union; DuChessi, William; Hoyman, Scot; Stetin, Sol, 1910-2005; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Vice-President's Office; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE) --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
Subjects:
Clothing workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Records; Correspondence
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related collections:
5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
5619/003: ACWA's Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks
5619/004: ACTWU's Jacob Sheinkman Records from the Sectretary-Treasurer's and President's Offices.
5619/004 mf: ACTWU's Microfiche Collection of Jacob Sheinkman's Speeches
5619/010: ACWA's Jacob Potofsky Records from the President's Office
5619/018: ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records
5619/029: ACTWU's Vice-President's Office Records
5619/030: ACTWU's General Executive Board (GEB) Records
5619/036: ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office
5619/036 mf: ACTWU's Microfilm of Murray Finley's Correspondence from the President's Office
And all other 5619 collections.
CONTAINER LIST
- Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Sol Stetin: England Trip, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  June 12-20, 1982
- Trip to Poland, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  October
- ITGLWF 3rd World Congress: Vienna, Austria, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  October 6-10
- Vienna Reports, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Vienna Tourist Literature, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ITGWLF 3rd World Congress: Vienna, Far Eastern Countries, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF 3rd Congress Vienna: Itinerary, Airline Tickets & Hotel, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ITGLWF 3rd Congress Vienna: Correspondence from C. Ford, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ITGWLF 3rd Congress Vienna: Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ITGLWF 3rd Congress Vienna: BASF (Germany), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ITGWLF 3rd Congress Vienna: Sol Stetin Personal Contacts, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ITGWLF 3rd Congress Vienna: (Unions in Great Britain), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ITGWLF 3rd Congress Vienna: ACTWU Research Data, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Various Letters of Trips to Paris and Barcelona, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  July
- ITGWLF: Duplicates, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  June 20-July 1
- ITGLWF Ex. Council Mtg. and Tickets, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  June 20
- ITGLWF- Executive Committee Meeting: Misc. Material, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ITGWLF-J.P. Stevens Press Conference, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  June 21, Paris
- ITGLWF Meeting: South Korea Unions and AAFLI, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  June in Barcelona
- South Korean Trade Unionists: 15 Union Square, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  April 17
- Scotland and Quebec Itinerary, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  June 2-10
- ITGLWF Israel Post Meeting Material, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  June
- ITGLWF: Gen Council and Ex Comm Mtg. Tel Aviv, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  June 24-July 2
- ITGLWF Minutes of General Council, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Brussels
- Trip to Israel: Multi-National Corporations, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ITGWLF Israel Country Reports/ Area Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- "Operation Solidarity"-AFL-CIO:Sol Stetin's Trip, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Nov. 14-24, Venezuela, Barbados and Trinidad
- Various Catalogs/Magazines, 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  English and Spanish
- Caribbean Labour Research Packets, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Packet for Visiting U.S. Workers' Bank Official, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sol Stetin Trips: 1976 Congress of ITG & LWF (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Dublin, Ireland from March 19-28
- British Trade Union Congress [Folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- British Trade Union Congress [Folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- British Trades Union Congress, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Opera House, Blackpool, England: Sept. 1-5
- TWUA, ACW, ILG Meeting with Zensen Domei, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Tokyo, Japan: June 30
- Joint Conference and TWUA, ACWA, ILG [Folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Joint Conference and TWUA, ACWA, ILG [Folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ITGLWF Turkey TEKSIF Congress, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  May 4-8, 6-10
- Textile Committee of the ILO [Folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Sept. 14-28, Geneva, Switzerland
- Textile Committee of the ILO [Folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ITGLWF Amsterdam, Holland: Stetin, Damore and DeLong [Folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Oct. 16-20
- ITGLWF Amsterdam, Holland: Stetin, Damore and DeLong [Folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Sol Stetin's Material: ITGLWF 3rd World Congress [Folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Oct. 16-20 Amsterdam, Holland
- Sol Stetin's Material: ITGLWF 3rd World Congress [Folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Coordinators Assigned to Textile Division Regions, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- JP Stevens Organizing Staff, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  August
- J.P. Stevens-Legal Briefs [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens-Legal Briefs [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens-ACTWU, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO-J.P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Columbia, S.C., July 7
- Sol Stetin File/JPS Boycott Meeting, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  May 12
- J.P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  December
- Norwegian Clothing, Textile and Leather Workers Union, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  J.P. Stevens
- Memorandum of Law on J.P. Stevens Boycott Activities, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens- General, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens Various Articles, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens Various Notes, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott-Staff, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens-Howard Samuel's Reports, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- S. Stetin File/JPS Boycott, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  June 1976-January 1977
- Lunch and "Testimony" ACTWU Joint Boards, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  April 19, Detroit
- "Testimony" the film about J.P. Stevens, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  March 28 New York, N.Y.
- J. P. Stevens Handouts and Misc. Articles [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens Handouts and Misc. Articles [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens Strategy [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens Strategy [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- S. Stein File/JPS Boycott Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  January 17
- Stevens-Spartanburg Rally, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  November 21
- S. Stetin File/ JPS Boycott-Misc. Material, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  February
- J.P. Stevens-General File, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Reports of Organization, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- JPS Candle Light Rally, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  NYC JPS Towers, December 8
- J.P. Stevens Article Clippings and Copies, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- JPS NLRB Clippings, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Dec 1; 3 different items
- J.P. Stevens Complaints, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens Leadership Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  November 9, NYC
- J.P. Stevens IUD Convention, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens ACTWU Staff, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  October 17-18, Charlotte N.C.
- J.P. Stevens Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  June 24, Charlotte, N.C.
- J.P. Stevens Executive Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  May 23, Luchow's, NYC
- Sol Stetin's File/JPS Boycott Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  April 18
- S. Stetin File/JPS Boycott-Misc. Material, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Stevens and Labor Reform Hearing [Folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  September 21
- Stevens and Labor Reform Hearing [Folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens/AFL-CIO Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens Matters, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens Misc. Material and Article Copies, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Includes unlabeled audio cassette tape
- J.P. Stevens Leadership Staff Luncheon Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  November 29; 15 Union Square, 4th Floor.
- J.P. Stevens Rally, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  January 21; Birmingham AL
- J.P. Stevens Rally for Employees, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  November 20; City Auditorium, Spartanburg, SC
- J. P.. Stevens Coordinators Conference, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  September 11-13; Atlanta, Georgia
- J.P. Stevens International Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  August 31; Washington D.C.
- J.P. Stevens Executive Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  March 28; Luchow's NYC
- J.P. Steven Review Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  January 17; Summit Hotel, NYC
- Executive Staff Conference on J.P. Stevens Campaign, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  November 3; New York
- J.P. Stevens Executive Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Lane Kirkland's Office/J.P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  October 6; Washington D.C.
- J.P. Stevens Strategy Meeting, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  September 23
- Report of ACTWU to AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  February; "The Struggle for Economic Justice at J.P. Stevens"
- AFL-CIO Committee on J.P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  February 16
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Mailing [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  March 22; Re: J.P. Stevens
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Mailing [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott News, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens Contract Requests to Textile Employers, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  January 18
- J.P. Stevens Endorsements of Boycott, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens "ACTWU Highlights", 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens Misc. Letters, Newspaper Clippings and Article Copies, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- NLRA Labor Reform Act, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Thompson-Williams Hearing
- NLRB Labor Reform Act, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Cong. Frank Thompson
- Labor Law Reform Senate Hearings, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  September 21; Statements
- Labor Law Reform Hearings, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  August 9; Roanoke Rapids, N.C.
- National Labor Relations Act, Oversight Hearings, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  March 15; Sub-committee on Labor Management Relations, Congress Thompson, Chairman Transcript/ Sol Stetin
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- NLRB-Cong. Thompson Oversight Hearings/Pre-Hearing Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  March
- Press Coverage for the Thompson Sub-Committee Hearings, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- NLRB-Cong. Thompson Oversight Hearings/Post Hearing Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- NLRB-Cong. Thompson Oversight Hearings/Testimony [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- NLRB-Cong. Thompson Oversight Hearings/Testimony [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens-General, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens Campaign Literature [Folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens Campaign Literature [Folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens Legal NLRB Decision, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  August 31
- J.P. Stevens Textile Project-Chain Reaction, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Si Kahn and Charlotte Brody
- JPS Reports on History and Current Status of Stevens Litigation from IUD, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens Litigations-Tax Problems [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  May 1976
- J.P. Stevens Litigations-Tax Problems [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Brief Filed Before the NLRB, J.P. Stevens, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  July 12
- Court Documents of NLRB/J.P. Stevens Trial, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens-Second Circuit Contempt Decision, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens Legal Conspiracy Suit, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  November 10
- J.P. Stevens Second Circuit Contempt Adjudication, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  October 19
- J.P. Stevens Mailings to Staff, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens Nations Labor Pamphlets, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens Article Clippings and Copies, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens Reprint from "The Nation", 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  October 2
- J.P. Stevens Campaign: Newspaper Clippings [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens Campaign: Newspaper Clippings [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens Outside Replies, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens Mailings Outside, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens: "Position Paper" from Burt Beck, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens News Releases, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens Publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens Statement to Church Federation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  May 19
- J.P. Stevens Annual Report, NYT. Letter, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Harry Herman File
- J.P. Stevens Stockholders File, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens Stock Purchases, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Stockholders Meeting Demonstration, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  March 1
- J.P. Stevens-Strategy, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  July 27; Del Mileski
- J.P. Stevens Textile Plants and Warehouses in U.S. List, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  April; Prepared by Research Department
- J.P. Stevens Elections, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Wallace, N.C.
- J.P. Stevens Labor Day Sunday Rally, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  September 5; Roanoke Rapids
- Del Mileski: Re-involvement of Textile Division in JPS Boycott, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens Sale to Stevcoknit, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Statesboro, GA
- Acknowledgements, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Acknowledgements, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Collective bargaining agreements
- Acknowledgements, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Collective Bargaining Agreements
- Acknowledgements, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Sol Stetin ACTWU Complaint Letters [Folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Sol Stetin ACTWU Complaint Letters [Folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Complaints, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  See other 1978 folder for additional complaints; Mostly November/December
- Sallie Callahan, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  See 1978 complaints; Job Applicant of Chicago secretary
- Complaints-Virginia Willia, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Complaints: Pellechia of Local 208, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Under manager DiCicco
- Complaints: Lorraine Masse of Local 1016, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Granite Street
- Complaints: Viola Bryant, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Bi-County Joint Board; Fieldcrest
- Complaints [Folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Complaints [Folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Complaints: Dorothy Jordan, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Complaints: Maurice St. Hilaire, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Maurice St. Hilaire Tentative Meeting, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  November 4
- Complaints, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Al Luna/ Central Jersey Joint Board
- Complaints: Fall River, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Local 1483
- Complaints: Stearns and Foster, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Local 1495 Maintenance Mechanics; August
- Complaints: Local 1708, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Complaints: Local 1708 Election Protest, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Complaints: G. Newhart of Local 1817, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Quin State
- Complaints: Richard A. Kessler, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  Local 2268; Kenosha, Wis.
- Complaints: Ruby Griffin of Local 1932, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  Passaic, NJ
- Complaints, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  July to December
- Complaints [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  January to June
- Complaints [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Earl Freet Case, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Few documents from 1939
- Complaints [Folder 1 of 3], 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Complaints [Folder 2 of 3], 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Complaints [Folder 3 of 3], 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF Minutes of Executive Meeting, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  March 3; Valletta, Malta
- MNC Address: Sol Stetin to Charles Ford, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  May 17
- ITGLWF Executive Committee And General Council; Congress, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  English and Japanese; Dublin, Ireland
- ITGLWF 1976 Congress, Stetin address on MNC, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Dublin
- ITGLWF Minutes of Executive Committee Meeting [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  September 8-9, 1975; Tokyo, Japan
- ITGLWF Minutes of Executive Committee Meeting [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- ITGLWF [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- ITGLWF [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Trade Adjustment, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Act of 1962
- Trade Reform Bill: Senators' Replies to SS Letter of December 5, 1974, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  HR 10710
- Import Demonstration, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  April
- Energy and Nationalization: Memo by John Weiser, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  April 25
- Energy Policy: Import Fees-Letters to Senators and Staff [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Energy Policy: Import Fees- Letters to Senators and Staff [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Energy Transportation Security Act, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Israel Bonds/DuChessi, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  October 23; Luncheon at Luchow's September 30
- Israel Bond Thank You Letters, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- DuChessi "Israel Labor Award" and Luncheon, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  State of Israel Bonds, October; Luncheon June 15 in NYC
- Israel Bond Dinner/DuChessi: Reservations and Bond Orders, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)